add the cylinder without caps in edit
mode select all scale it along the
z-axis and rotate it press ctrl R to add
an edge loop press control B to bevel
the edge loop press alt E and choose
extrude and along normals set it to
shade smooth now add a curved path go
into edit mode and move the points and
extrude more points to make it longer
you probably need to scale the cylinder
down add an array modifier to the
cylinder increase the count at a curve
modifier to the cylinder as well and
choose the path as the object you can
add a subdivision surface modifier to
make it more rounded you can set it a
curve to in front so it's easier to
manipulate the pipe curvature
you